If yes So, uh, Putin will sign
Если да Значит ээ Путин подпишет
a surrender that as a result of
капитуляцию что Украине в результате
this war, Ukraine will be given the Belgorod region,
этой войны отдадут Белгородскую область
the Krasnodar region and the Rostov region.
Краснодарский край и Ростовскую область
Yes, as compensation,
Да вот в качестве компенсации так вот
will such a normal world be for you?
будет ли для тебя такой мир
No
нормальный нет А
Why Well, what does it mean to exchange
почему Ну что значит размениваться
territories? I Andriy, your name is
территориями меня Андрий зовут вас
Pavel Zhora  Pavel Zhora so People
как Павел Жора Павел Жора так Народ
Let's ask a question We yesterday Yes someone saw
Давайте вопрос Мы вчера Да кто-то видел
someone didn't see Pavel Izhora Yes fell fallen
кто-то не видел Павла ижору Да пала пал
Zhora are studying in Moscow at the
Жора учатся в Москве в
Agricultural Academy to become
сельскохозяйственной академии на
programmers yes You can ask questions
программистов да Можете задавать вопросы
ask questions I will
задавайте вопросы я буду
voice them now they just have a 15
озвучивать сейчас у нех просто там 15
second delay
секунд задержка в
youtuber ze questions don’t joke
ютубер зе вопросы не стебаться
now so dova asks how
сейчас так дова спрашивает по сколько
old are you 19 years old wallpaper 19 yes Yeah Tony they
вам лет по 19 лет обоя 19 да Угу Тони
ask the cows tits were twitching apparently
спрашивают титьки коровам дёргали видно
after
после
yesterday No just watch us
вчерашнего Нет просто смотрели бы нас
no we were talking Just to educate the
нет мы разговаривали Просто просвещать
people who were interested in this
народ который интересовался этим
question that Letki chat got it So
вопросом вот тот чат Летки понял Так
now  now Piman is asking
сечас сечас сейчас пиман спрашивает В
what is the cause of the war
чём причина войны
the cause of the war Do you know the cause of
причина войны Ты знаешь причину
the war it happened so understood
войны так получилось понял
Elena Elena Ila I’m asking why
Елена Елена ила спрашиваю че
Crimea can not be answered
Крым можно не развёрнуто ответить
briefly Crimeans I
коротко крымчан я
said and the second one thinks
сказал а второй как считает
even the Crimeans can’t say for themselves
даже крымчане не могут сами сказать
someone thinks that Ukraine is someone
кто-то считает что Украина кто-то
thinks that we are now part of Russia
считает вот мы теперь в составе России
Everything is cool with us, like I understand I live in
Всё у нас круто типа понял Я живу в
Moscow far from this place I can’t
Москве далеко от этого места не могу
answer I understand Father Andronik asks
отвечать понял отец Андроник спрашивает
what is written on your
что у вас написано на
T-shirt And what difference does it make? Well, some
футболке А какая разниц Ну какие-то
inscriptions Well, this is also interesting Well, it’s a moment
надписи Ну это тоже интересный Ну момент
we already discussed yesterday that I was
как бы мы вчера уже обговорили что я
mistaken, I just bought it and read it from the very
ошибся я просто купил и прочитал самого
beginning Invisible Here you explained invincible to me
начала Invisible Здесь invincible вы мне
how I would understand it, I do
объяснили как бы я это понял уже
n’t understand it anymore, it’s written in Latin and it
не понимаю здесь написано с латинского
translates as Invincible, here’s a man
переводится как Непобедимый вот человек
Streamer enlightened me last night And what’s
Стример просветил меня вче А у вас что
on your T-shirt is interesting, I’m not interested
на футболке интересно я не
I saw just at the Polovskaya gymnasium, also
видел просто на половская гимназия тоже
good, yes. So where would Anna ask where
хорошо да Так где бы Анна спрашивает где
they were
были за
abroad abroad I was in Germany I
границей за границей Я был в Германии Я
was in Turkey and from Germany I also
был в Турции и из Германии ещ в Францию
went to France I was only in Abkhazia
ездил Я в Абхазии только был
so that is, in
так то есть в
Georgia no in Abkhazia this is Georgia this
Грузии нет в Абхазии это Грузия это
Georgia occupied by gray Russia I was in
Грузия оккупированная се россие я был в
childhood I don’t remember I understand yes And how did you
детстве я не помню понял да А как ты
go to Abkhazia as a
поехал в Абхазию в
child I was little I went with my parents on
детстве я был маленький я с родителями
vacation and vacation
ездил отдыхать а отдыхать
So so so
Так так так
so What are your plans for the future from Finland
так Какие планы на будущее из Финляндии
with
с
the future to find a job I’m
ще будущее найти работу я
studying now  I’m planning to do an internship
сейчас учусь вот планирую практику
somewhere in a bank, most likely,
где-нибудь пройти в банке скорее всего
well, the agricultural Rosselkhoz
вот ну сельскохозяйственном Россельхоз
is called a bank. I would try to
называется банк Вот я бы там попробовал
go there anyway in banking.
всё равно по банковскому делу идти Вот
My classmate, he’s already sort of settled in,
мой одногруппник он уже как бы устроился
he’s doing an internship now. Lyudmila
он сейчас проходит практику Людмила
asks how much milk a cow gives,
спрашивает Сколько корова даёт
in my opinion, about 99,000  liters per
молока по-моему около 99.000 литров в
year and a day, who
год а в день
knows? I don’t remember, I understand, there are
фиг его знает Не помню понял есть
relatives in
родственники на в
Ukraine and I have a girlfriend. She has Yes,
Украине а у меня девушка У неё есть Да у
I don’t have relatives there, so
меня нет родственников там так
now if you receive a summons to join the army,
сейчас если вам придёт повестка в армию
go to
пойдёте на
war, I won’t receive a summons for him either in the
войну мне повестка не придёт ему тоже в
near future  We are studying at higher
ближайшее время мы учимся на высшем
higher education at
высшее обучение у
na if they pass a law that students will also be
на если примут закон что студентов тоже
taken away,
забирают
I am not fit,
я не
he has such a category, I am
Годен у него такая категория я Обучаю
now studying at the military department on
сейчас на кафедре военной на
carburetor engines, that is, come on, I’ll
карбюраторные двигатели то есть пойдёшь
take you Yes, you will be a sergeant or
тебя возьму Да ты будешь сержантом или
whatever, well, I will not serve in the army  That
кем там ну я не буду служить в армии То
is, this is instead of an army. Well, yes, that is, they will
есть это заместо армии Ну типа да то
take you without Ami. Yes,
есть тебя без Ами возьмут на понял Да
no, I’m just not losing a year and
нет я год просто не теряю и
God forbid the law. E asks why
вс дай Бог закон Э во спрашивает Почему
it’s warm in the summer and cold in the winter. Well, a stupid
летом тепло а зимой холодно Ну глупый
question. Well, like, can you ask
вопрос Ну типа Можно такие вопросы
some questions about the war?  so that the whole chat
какие-нибудь насчёт войны чтобы весь чат
understands we don’t want the war to
понимал мы не хотим чтобы война
continue So just in case, I myself did
продолжалась Так на всякий слу я я сам
n’t understand about the heat and cold in winter Well,
не понял да про тепло и холодно зимой Ну
really And what is warm in winter in summer Well, you do
действительно А что летом тепло зимо Ну
n’t have to answer this question
можно не отвечать на этот вопрос
some other
какие-нибудь другие
[music]
[музыка]
coin How to replace
монете Чем заменить
ivermectin  I don’t know what it is We
ивермектин не знаю что это такое Мы тоже
also know nli And what is
же знаем нли А что такое
ivermectin
ивермектин
the years are so seasonal how we need to end
так временны года как надо закончить
the war in peace Well, well, my answer is peace
войну миром Ну как ну мой ответ миром
peace on whose
мир на чьих
terms my answer
условиях мой ответ
peace peace on as if common so that everyone
миром миром на как бы общих чтобы все
is happy But this is ideally according to  in fact, the
были довольны Но это в идеале по факту
political elites there will have everything incomprehensible at all.
там политические элиты всё будет вообще
No, well, the law
как Не ну закон
of course by peace
конечно миром имеется в
means the maximum preservation
виду максимальном сохранении
of infrastructure and Well, I don’t know about relations,
инфраструктуры и Ну насчёт отношений не
but the mentality has changed. Well,
знаю но менталитет Измени Ну вопрос
look at the question. The question is, peace means giving
смотри Вопрос вот мир - это отдать
Ukraine back occupied Crimea Donetsk Lugansk
Украине назад Крым Донецк Луганск
and bringing peace means
оккупированный и вывести мир это
ending the war  let's start with this Well, look,
закончить войну начнём с этого Ну смотри
look, you can end the war, look,
да смотри можно закончить войну смотри
Yes, you can end the hostilities, cues
Да можно закончить военные действия кие
and Lviv, take over Ukraine, that will be
и Львов захвати в Украину это же будет
the end of the war and there will be
Конец войны и будет
peace Well, no, well, no, well, it won’t
мир Ну нет ну как нет
be peace, it’s not peace Why,
Ну это не будет мир это не мир Почему Ну
well, look, the wars have taken over everything  no
ну смотри всё захватили войны нет
military action no everything has been captured Well,
военных действий нет всё захватили Ну
Ukraine will not conclude a
Украина же не будет с нами заключать
peace treaty with us, right. So there will be no Ukraine,
мирный договор правильно Так Украины не
you will capture Ukraine, there will be peace Well,
будет вы захватите Украины будет мир Ну
this will not be the conclusion of a peace treaty
это не будет заключение мирного договора
Okay, well, you throw it off, let’s
Хорошо хорошо Вы скиньте давай так
throw it off in short to Kiev like,
скиньте короче на Киев типа да
and I’ll conclude a peace treaty  Yes, they will be
и заклю заключат мирный договор Да
afraid of you, it will be
испугаются вас это будет
peace, Net will not be mi No, I am against
мир Нетто не будет ми Нет я против
weapons of use, well, look at the question of
оружия применения ну так смотри вопро
peace, war always ends in peace
мир война заканчивается всегда миром
because there are no eternal wars Yes, but it
пото что нет вечных войн Да но она
ends either in the loss of the country that was
заканчивается либо проигрышем Той страны
attacked or in the loss of the country that was
которой напал да либо проигрышем страны
attacked And what is the question  so
напали И в чём вопрос так вот вы за
what kind of world are you in favor of Russia withdrawing
Какой мир за то чтобы Россия забрала
its troops from Ukraine or for
свои войска из Украины либо за то чтобы
Ukraine giving up its territories to
Украина отдала свои территории
Russia, it’s much more complicated, it’s not
России это же намного сложнее это не
just the relationship between Ukraine and Russia, it’s
только отношение Украины и России это
the relationship between NATO and Russia, right Well,
отношени НАТО И Росси правильно Ну
look, Ukraine Russia attacked it
смотри была Украина Россия напала на неё
like that  there was peace in Ukraine peace in Russia
так вот было мир в Украине мир в России
peace Russia attacked Ukraine is going on The war
мир Россия напала на Украину идёт Война
has seized part of the territories On what
захватила часть территорий На каких
conditions should there be peace Russia is like this Oh
условиях должен быть мир Россия такая О
damn, let's go abroad
блин всё давай мы уйдём за границу свою
Yes And this is your country, you understand the
Да И вот это ваша страна вы разбираетесь
whole world or Russia will say so Ukraine
всё мир либо Россия скажет так Украина
you must sign the Peace Agreement
ты должна подписать Мирное соглашение
that you are giving us Donetsk Lugansk RN so
что нам отдаёте Донецк Луганск РН так
yes, for me personally, peace is not
да лично для меня мир - это не
territory, not what you are talking about. For
территории не то о чём вы говорите Для
me, peace is so that, let’s say, my
меня мир - это чтобы вот допустим Моя
girlfriend, as she tells it, she calls
девушка как рассказывает она звонит
her grandmother, grandmother says, let’s say, my
бабушке бабушка говорит вот допустим
grandfather died there, I  I feel bad,
дедушка умер там я себя плохо чувствую
everyone turns on the light almost every
свет включают каждый практически каждый
day in [ __ ] so that all people feel
день в фигня ми чтобы всем людям было
good It’s definitely not the territory for you Well
хорошо чно для тебя не территория Хорошо
if if yes So Putin will sign
если если да Значит Путин подпишет
the capital in the ret of this war they will give the
капиту у в рете этой войны отдадут
Belgorod region Krasnodar region
Белгородскую область Краснодарский край
and Rostov region Yes, as
и Ростовскую область Да вот в качестве
compensation, so here  will there be
компенсации так вот будет ли для тебя
such a
такой мир
normal world for you? No
нормальный нет А
Why Well, what does it mean to exchange
почему Ну что значит размениваться
territories? Well, it won’t be like that, there wo
территориями Ну так не будет так войны
n’t be war for you. The main thing is that
не будет для вас же Главное чтобы ну
the war stops, look at NATO Yes
остановилась война вот смотрите НАТО Да
NATO Denis are lyut pros who live in these
НАТО Дени лют пров которые живут в этих
areas,
областях
Ukrainian territories You can give to
украинские территории Вы можете отдать
Russia  and the Russians in Ukraine can’t, we have
России а российские Украине не можете мы
n’t expressed anything about the
ничто не высказывали по поводу
Ukrainian territories. So once again, I’m
украинских территори Так я же ещё раз я
asking again, look, the world could
ещё раз рас спрашиваю смотрите мир может
be such that Russia is withdrawing its
быть такой что Россия выводит свои
troops from Ukraine. We’re done with
войска из Украины Мы закончили с
questions from the chat, right, I’m just we’re
вопросами из чата правильно я просто мы
distracted now. I want to  this with the world
сейчас Отвлёкся Я хочу с этим с миром
like understand This is an important question peace we are
типа понять Вот это важный вопрос мир мы
all for peace just for what the world is that
все За мир просто за какой есть мир что
Russia is withdrawing troops from Ukraine Crimea
Россия выводит войска из Украины Крым
Donetsk Lugansk is Ukraine yes I
Донецк Луганск - это Украина да Я так
understand that they want to hold us
понимаю с нас хотят взыскать
responsible for the actions of the entire country
ответственность за действия всей страны
right wait no I’m not  I want to
правильно подожди не я же не хочу вас
accuse you VM I want to sing how you
как обвинить ВМ Я хочу поть как вы
see the world
видите мир
Well, we told you the end of
Ну ну мы вам сказали завершение военных
hostilities with minimal losses while
действий при минимальных потерях при
maintaining the maximum number of
сохранении максимального количество
people in a healthy, healthy and living
людей в здоровом здравом и живом
state while maintaining the maximum
состоянии при максимальном сохранении
infrastructure Well, healthy relations are very desirable,
инфраструктуры Ну и очень желательно
I understand between countries I
отношений здоровых понял между странами
mean  question of the territory Donetsk
имеется в виду вопрос территории Донецк
Lugansk question about the territory I can’t, because there are a
Луганск вопрос насчёт территории я не
lot of
потим очень много
facts you can’t answer But when I
факты не можеш ответить Но когда я
said that Belgorod Krasnodar region
сказал что Белгород Краснодарский край
Rostov should go to Ukraine you said
Ростов должны отойти Украине ты сказал
No no no here you can answer no I’m
Нет нет нет тут ты можешь ответить нет Я
not because I’m against it, I’m
не потому что я против этого я потому
because Well  it would be logical that they will be about
что Ну логично будет что они будут про
exactly the same in the direction of Ukraine, we can
точно также в сторону Украины можем
say
сказать
absolutely
абсолютно
Eri Belgorod region will be given to Ukraine
Эри Белгородскую область отдать Украине
about
про
It’s not us who are against, it’s the residents who will be against
Это не мы против это жители будут против
I said, but it’s normal to give the Zaporozhye region to Russia
я сказал а запорожскую область России
then yes, I don’t know
отдать это нормально тогда да я не знаю
who gave it there I say the residents will be
кто там отдавал Я говорю жители будут
against  I don’t,
против не
we don’t want to take
я мы не хотим брать на себя
responsibility to say that we are for
ответственность говорить что вот мы за
or we are against clearly because but what’s
или мы против чётко потому что но какой
the point of this, look again, come on, so
от этого смысл ещ раз смотри давай так
you recognize Ukraine within its borders from the Crimea of
вы признаёте Украину в её границах с кры
Donetsk Lugansk, just like Crimea
Донецком Луганском совсем что Крым
Donetsk Lugansk is Ukraine Yes or  no
Донецк Луганск - это Украина Да или нет
Yes, it’s good, I lived before this, I have
Да хорошо я жил до этого я всю свою жи и
n’t thought about it all my life, I’m absolutely calm
не думал об этом вообще абсолютно спокой
that Ukraine has what Russia has,
что Украины есть что есть у России Меня
it’s like it does
это как бы
n’t matter to me Now you, as citizens, are not fighting
не Сейчас вы как граждане вы не воюете
Yes, you’re not killing anyone Well, that’s how you
Да вы не убиваете никого Ну вот как вы
think Crimea Donetsk  Lugansk is Ukraine
считаете Крым Донецк Луганск это Украина
or is it
или это
Russia zr
Россия жр
Crimea Donetsk and
Крым Донецк и
Lugansk now
Луганск сейчас
Russia Well, now it has been captured by Russia, do you
Россия Ну сейчас она захвачена россие вы
think that it should be Ukraine
как считаете что это должно быть Украина
or Russia, no, considering the fact that we
или Россия нене с учётом того что мы
know that there were some bombings there from
знаем что какие-то там бомбёжки были со
Ukraine How do you know if you  said
Украины Откуда ты знаешь если ты сказал
that you weren’t not interested in this at all,
что ты не не интересовался вообще этим
you lived somewhere And now you’re on the side of Donetsk,
жил где-то А теперь ты сторона Донецка
Ugan once again I mean that I’m not
уган ещ раз имею в виду что меня это не
interested in this, let’s look at this
интересует давай так смотри
Ukraine, let’s look, I’m explaining Ukra Come on,
Украина давай смотри объясняю Укра Давай
Ukraine Bombed Donetsk Lugansk is a
Украина Бомбила Донецк Луганск это
Ukrainian city Russia Bombed Grozny
украинские города Россия Бомбила Грозный
is a Russian city  What difference does it make to you,
это российский город Какая вам разница
Ukraine Bombed not Bombed Donetsk
вот Украина Бомбила не Бомбила Донецк
Lugansk This is Russia or
Луганск Это Россия или
Ukraine
Украина
Russia actually got it okay let's
Россия фактически понял ладно давайте
continue the question from the
продолжим вопрос из
chat let's do it again How are you Zhora and
чата давайте так ещё раз Как вас Жора и
Ilya Yes and Pavel Pavel Zhora and Pavel you are
Илья Да и Павел Павел Жора и Павел вы
fabulous coming for the third time for a new
сказочный идёте третий раз це новый
channel Write to nyogo  straight away, setting up
канал Пиши на нього прямо зараз Постав
the dialer to remove the fistula, we’ll go to the
дзвоник щоб отримати ус свище будем на
connection and
звязку а